The events of this movie happen between episodes 151 and 152. Do not watch before episode 151.
Minors are advised to watch with the consent of their guardians.
This is a work of fiction. The events depicted, including the cultivation system, are entirely fictional.
Do not attempt to imitate this in real life.
Adapted from the webnovel "Renegade Immortal" by Er Gen, an author on Qidian.
200 years ago,
Publisher
Shun Huaizhong
in search of legendary treasures,
countless cultivators left their sects
Chief Planner
Cui Chao
Chief Executive Producer
Ma Yankun
and headed to the treacherous Demon Spirit Land.
Producers
Zhang Jianning
Yan Lihua
Supervisor Producers
Feng Yi
Zhou Wang
That place was full of hidden dangers.
When surrounded by powerful enemies,
people's intentions are unpredictable.
Marketing Coordinators
Liu Yazheng
Hemeng Jie
Operations Coordinators
Xia Xiaotong
Wu Junda
Li Yang
One misstep meant death and the end of the road.
Commercial Coordinators
Long Yezhao
Wang Wei
Most knew they were no match
and resolved to head back.
But one man
Head Writer
Ma Hua
Writers
Li Qingyue
Liu Mengwei
Wang Ziyue
was different.
Even in such a place,
his resolve remained unwavering.
Head Director
Shi Touxiong
For the sake of his convictions,
Directors
Wang Jianxin
Li Zhenfeng
he advanced step by step
within the Demon Spirit Land
to overpower his rivals.
Until he finally...
Directing Team
Cui Wei       Du Wenkai
Jinjia Rong   Zhang Zhe
Zhang Wan     Naxiang Xiang
Wang Dong     Lin Junyue
Liu Zhu       Zhao Yong
reached Ascendant.
Executive Producer
Wang Junchao
Production Director
Zhang Shipei
Tong Ye
Jade Sword Sect member
Little Ye,
we must persevere.
Lu Zhao
Jade Sword Sect member
There is hope
if we persevere !
Senior Brother...
Search !
Jade Sword Sect
Alliance Star System
Don't let any of them escape !
Don't be afraid,
stay silent.
Li Jiu
Blood Guardian
Blood Planet
S...Senior Brother...
Found them !
L...Little Ye...
Renegade Immortal
Battle of the Immortal Slayer
Subtitles by Bonobosubs https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Wang Lin's avatar
Peak Late stage Ascendant
Thunder Beast
Using thunder stones to temper my body
has yielded some slight progress.
But the second step
still remains out of reach.
Forget it,
no need to rush.
Blood connection !
This is bad !
Wang Lin,
Yao Xixue
Blood Ancestor's daughter
Late stage Soul Transformation
I endured the humiliation and prepared for 100 years
for this day to arrive !
Blood Blade,
activate !
Wang Lin,
you stole my fortuitous opportunity
and imprisoned me until now.
You deserve to die !
Restriction,
break !
That day, you broke your promise
and tried to kill me first.
If I hadn't fought back,
you would've killed me a long time ago.
This woman is vicious.
If I release her,
her father will surely come to seek revenge.
Stop !
But if I kill her,
she will use a Blood Soul Pill to revive elsewhere.
Wang Lin,
you're despicable and shameless !
Suppress !
Your current situation
is nothing but your own doing.
You deserve it.
I deserve it ?
My father is a Nirvana Cleanser powerhouse.
I was born to stand above all others !
How dare you judge me !?
Wang Lin,
one day,
I'm going to tear you to pieces !
I can't kill her
nor release her.
She is a ticking time bomb
that will bring endless trouble.
I must find Li Yuan as soon as possible to repair the seal.
I can't delay it.
The blood connection is complete.
It's too late, Wang Lin.
It's already too late.
Senior Brother...
Senior Brother !
Move !
Blood Hall
Blood Planet
Alliance Star System
Lord Blood Ancestor,
as you ordered,
all cultivators from the 300 cultivation planets nearby
have been captured and brought here.
Go ahead and place the seal.
Blood Slave Seal,
fall !
By my blood,
I bind you all
to be my slaves for all eternity.
Blood Ancestor
Nirvana Cleanser
Take them away.
My husband's divine might
is a fortuitous opportunity for these lower realm cultivators
to become the foundation of your spells.
I noticed you've been troubled lately.
Zi Xin
You must be worried about Xixue.
Husband, please calm down.
This concubine spoke out of turn.
This concubine...
This concubine was foolish
and only wished to share your burdens.
Although I have an Allheaven Stone,
the Allheaven Star System is vast.
Without coordinates to guide me,
finding Xixue
is like finding a needle in a haystack.
That useless Greed !
He's been in the Allheaven Star System for so long,
yet he hasn't sent back any useful information.
Xixue,
where are you exactly ?
When will Father hear from you ?
A blood connection !?
Father, save me !
Xixue...
She's actually in the Thunder Celestial Realm !
Defend the Blood Planet for me.
Yao
Yao Family ?
This is...
the all-powerful family of the Allheaven Star System,
the Yao Family.
Teleportation Formation
Allheaven Star System
Who dares to trespass !?
The Yao Family's Blood Guards
welcome Young Master Yao Kong back to the family.
Let's go
back to the family.
Yao Family's Ancestral Home
Allheaven Star System
Kong'er
pays respect to the Ancestor.
Blood God
Your father made a vow here back then.
He said even later generations would never come back.
Yao
Luodong
At the time, I told him:
"Luodong,
our Yao Family is bound by blood.
It can't be severed."
You see ?
Wasn't I correct ?
Grandfather,
your grandson has come back
for your great-granddaughter Xixue.
A lower realm ant named Wang Lin
ignored the Yao Family and schemed to harm her.
He stole her fortuitous opportunity
and imprisoned her for hundreds of years.
She is currently trapped in the Thunder Celestial Realm.
The gate to the Celestial Realm is currently closed.
I beg Grandfather to help me enter
and rescue Xixue !
That way, I...
will tear him to pieces !
Kong'er,
you established your own sect
and called yourself an Ancestor ?
How impressive.
And now,
you can't even protect your own daughter ?
You...
What you lost isn't your reputation
but the blood flowing in your veins,
the blood of my Yao Family !
However,
the people of my Yao Family,
no matter how unworthy,
will not be thrown away for outside dogs to bite.
The Blood God token !
This token is equivalent to my presence.
Yao
Let them all see
what happens to those who harm the Yao Family's bloodline !
As for this token's secret spell of melting the soul into blood...
You
are aware of its importance.
Kong'er,
the Yao Family's reputation
isn't something we begged for.
It was earned
with lives.
Grandson accepts the order !
A peerless Turtle Breath Pill !
Thunder won't strike you down,
beasts won't gnaw on you.
Take a pill if in danger
to stay safe !
Thunder Evading Market
Thunder Celestial Realm
Customer !
Take a look !
Li Yuan
Peak Late stage Ascendant
Brother Xu ?
What happened ?
I need to borrow your spiritual energy
to suppress the blood energy.
Understood.
Thunder Celestial Realm Gate
The Celestial Gate is closed !
Trespassers...
We pay respects to Senior of the Yao Family.
Xixue,
Father has come to take you home.
Hold on !
It's severed !?
Since the blood connection is lost,
then I will search every corner of every fragment
of the Thunder Celestial Realm !
It's stable for now.
This place is called the Thunder Evading Market.
It's a refuge built brick by brick
by countless cultivators unwilling to accept their fate.
The strong remain strong.
And the weak
must find ways to survive.
Just like me back then...
If not for Brother Xu...
If it weren't for Brother Xu's righteous help back then,
I wouldn't have dispelled the celestial slave imprint
nor broken out of my shackles
to be reborn.
I, Li Yuan,
would have long had my soul scattered.
I wouldn't be studying restrictions here today,
in search of peace and silence.
It wasn't anything big,
Brother Li doesn't have to dwell on it.
It may have been nothing for Brother Xu,
but for me,
it was a life-saving favor.
I will,
never forget this favor.
Come, come !
The last 10 Turtle Breath Pills !
No matter how strong the thunder, it won't kill you !
A Turtle Breath Pill ?
Lang Xing
Late stage Soul Transformation
Indeed !
A life-saving treasure !
Have a look !
Take another look !
No way, no way.
These 10 pills...
You've been shouting about them for a month now.
And no one will recognize their quality.
This is pretty good stuff you know ?
Brother Li,
I haven't seen this fellow cultivator before.
First time ?
This is my friend,
Xu Mu.
He's here to look around.
So it's Brother Xu.
Here are some Turtle Breath Pills.
With these,
even Peak Late stage Soul Transformation cultivators aren't scary.
Not here either.
Wang Lin,
let's see how long you can hide !
What's this ?
Nirvana Cleanser blood-colored killing intent ?
Go !
This place
returns to ruins.
Kneel.
Xixue's aura !
I finally found you.
Hand over Xixue !
Fall !
Li Yuan !
Annihilation Restriction Heart !
To the teleportation formation !
Quick !
Teleportation formation !
Hurry !
Hurry up !
Go !
Futile resistance.
Xu Liguo !
Hey !
Don't get too cocky, you old demon !
Xu Liguo
Grandpa Xu will fight you !
I can't win...
Grandpa Xu will go ahead first !
Wait for me !
Go !
He's gone...
Killing you is easy.
I'll let you live
while I search for Xixue's soul.
Try to run away ?
No one here
can escape my grasp !
I can smell it.
This is the scent of Father's blood spells.
Wang Lin,
I can also sense your fear.
What ?
Will you wag your tail
and let me go ?
Or do you want to kneel
and beg me to put in a good word with Father
to spare your pathetic life !?
You can dream !
I can convince Father to let you live a little more,
to suffer day by day,
unable to die !
It seems
no matter what,
my fate will be the same.
I'm glad you understand.
Killing me is the same as releasing me.
And if you seal me somewhere,
you'll face my father's endless pursuit !
One day,
when my father finds you,
I'll get out of here !
There is no way out.
Only one of us can live.
Are you looking for this ?
The situation was critical earlier
so I retrieved it for you.
However precious a restriction may be,
it can't compare to a mother's love.
Li Yuan thanks Brother Xu
for retrieving this charm of mine.
No need for thanks.
I risked my life !
You should be thanking me !
Brother Xu,
forgive my bluntness.
The Yao Family of Allheaven
is very powerful
and rules with an iron fist.
Those who defy it have to pay with their blood.
This is a common consensus throughout the Allheaven Star System.
Those who offend them
are either kept alive as Blood Slaves
or become pools of blood.
There are no exceptions.
That man's cultivation is Nirvana Cleanser.
Just now, I unleashed my Restriction Heart at full power
with 4 layers of Annihilation Restrictions,
but holding him back even for an instant was so difficult.
On the cultivation path,
the difference of a single realm is an uncrossable bridge,
let alone multiple realms at a time.
Brother Xu,
you...
It's a life or death situation now.
Brother Xu,
if you trust me,
I will use all the restrictions I've studied in my life
to give you a sliver of a chance of escaping.
It seems
I'm being targeted by such a powerhouse...
Is running my only way out ?
This...
Where are we ?
Weren't we supposed to be on a fragment of the Thunder Celestial Realm ?
Giant trees and plants still lush without roots...
Frozen butterflies...
This place
is a harmonious whole.
I had finally found a quiet place to sleep...
Master Flamespark
Peak Nirvana Shatterer
So noisy...
they disturbed my sleep.
Brother Xu,
when we teleported,
the Thunder Escaping Market's teleportation formation nearly collapsed
and clashed with the spatial energy of my Li family's Annihilation Restriction.
That's why
we were thrown into this place.
These two little guys
are somewhat interesting.
One
smells like restrictions,
he has a great inheritance !
Boring.
The other one
has an uncomfortable bloody smell on him.
He's targeted by those bloodsuckers of the Yao Family.
Such bad luck...
He's actually quite perceptive.
He's far better than those idiots in the Temple.
Since you've landed in my hands,
no matter how you are,
I will shape you by my rules.
Especially you, kid.
You even have a hint of thunder.
Don't let Grandpa
be too disappointed.
A self-contained world
but not like a Celestial's cave.
This place...
what is it ?
Excellent... excellent !
Run around,
jump around,
let me see how long you can hop around.
A Nirvana Shatterer old monster !
If you're too slow,
you will die.
I have no grudge with this person.
Why ?
Wonderful, wonderful !
That sudden movement
was executed with perfect precision.
Unfortunately,
you're too slow
and too conventional !
Grandpa isn't entertained !
Pure Yang Thunder ?
Cold Ice Thunder ?
Spatial Dark Thunder !
His thunder spells have reached perfection.
This person must be deeply connected to the Thunder Celestial Temple.
If he wanted to kill me,
it would be easy.
Why does he go to such lengths ?
It's as if
he were toying with me.
I can't let him lead me around any longer !
Since you use thunder,
I'll break it with thunder !
Senior,
you wouldn't go to such lengths
if you just wanted to kill me.
Why are you bothering with all this ?
If you're toying with me like this,
maybe you've taken a fancy for my meager skills ?
Are you
trying to test my limits ?
You're a good kid.
Grandpa was just bored
and just wanted to see what you're made of.
As expected,
a little guy that those bloodsuckers of the Yao Family covet
has some death-defying toughness in his bones.
You have guts.
You have quick wits.
The more I look at you,
the more I feel you are fated with me.
Suitable souls are hard to find
yet I happened to encounter such a fated beast.
Little guy,
not bad.
But it's mine now.
Senior !
What's the rush ?
I always act fairly.
I dislike being in debt for no reason
and I dislike being owed.
Since I've taken your Thunder Beast,
I've already given you a gift.
Take your time to enlighten yourself.
That old monster...
has already given me a gift ?
What did he give me ?
Rootless trees...
Sourceless water...
A self-contained world...
Unique laws...
This place isn't natural
but the inside of a masterless bag of holding.
I've already given you a gift.
So that's how it is !
Brother Li,
wake up.
I know where we are.
That's right...
That's right !
It contains the heavens and the earth,
everything is frozen,
rootless trees
and sourceless water.
There's no mistake !
Brother Xu,
This must be the place mentioned in ancient records whose inheritance was cut off.
Celestial's bag of holding
It's a Celestial's bag of holding !
I understand now.
The key to leaving is
a reverse restriction !
Since this place defies common sense,
we must take the opposite approach.
Just like our bags of holding,
once a living being is captured inside,
it can't leave from within.
Only by opening the bag from the outside
can we exit it.
Right now, we are inside the bag.
We only need to use a reverse restriction
to turn inner energy into outer energy.
That way, the bag will open !
It's said this bag isolates inside from outside.
Once its master dies,
it's forever cut off from the outside.
Thanks to the passage of time,
this entrance became unstable
and a crack formed.
All my life, I've waited for an opportunity like this
to enter and have a look inside !
Brother Li,
you said that
this item isolates the inside from the outside.
Then no matter one's cultivation,
it's absolutely impossible to enter or exit.
Am I correct ?
The records say that
for a self-contained world
with complete laws,
that's indeed the case.
Brother Li,
If this place can't be entered or exited without the proper method,
then if this world were to collapse,
wouldn't everything within
shatter with it ?
You...
Don't tell me you're thinking of...
That's right.
I want to use this place to kill the Blood Ancestor.
What do you think ?
Slaying an Immortal...
Brother Xu,
are you aware of what you're saying ?
That's a Nirvana Cleanser !
An old monster who has lived countless years !
Are you sure you want to do this ?
You're crazy,
completely crazy !
But Brother Xu,
you once saved my life,
severed the slave imprint,
and helped me regain my freedom !
If you want to do this,
how could I, Li Yuan,
just stand by and watch !?
I, Li Yuan, am fortunate enough
to take part in such a feat !
This may be my Li Family's restrictions
best resting place !
Brother Xu,
for this deed,
I, Li Yuan,
will lend you my full support !
Brother Xu,
with this heaven and earth as the board
and the stars as pieces,
we'll connect all the collapse points together
to this sky net.
One pull will blow the whole thing !
The net needs a backbone
and a sharp edge !
Thunder for the main destruction ?
Good !
This is a fine trap for slaying an Immortal !
Brother Xu,
This sphere contains
1973 collapse points.
I entrust it to you.
They...
are eternally sealed here.
Even if it’s a moment of peace,
they've lost the heavens, the earth, and their future.
If we fail,
will we
turn that moment of peace into nothingness ?
It's a moment of barely surviving,
what is there to cherish ?
Moreover,
Wind blows, the clouds bid farewell,
we may not lose.
Even if the odds point to
we part in silence.
a certain death with no chance of survival ?
Brother Li,
No need to speak of sorrow,
you go first.
Brother Xu, I...
Brother Li,
I've had the good fortune of sharing this journey with you.
you have a reason to go back.
You don't need to gamble everything with me.
Life and death are as light as a feather,
while the bond we forged in desperation is heavier than I thought.
Rather than scheming and manipulating,
let’s speak frankly and open our hearts to one another.
My son, you must return safely.
This toast to adversity... what does it matter
These
are concealment and stealth restrictions I collected.
if your most radiant silhouette journeys by my side.
They aren't an inheritance of the Li Family,
but they are all secret techniques
and very mysterious !
Keep them, they will surely be useful !
Life and death clash fiercely within the cup, fighting recklessly, not giving up, unyielding.
Okay.
Then let me blaze a trail to overturn the terrifying waves.
Brother Xu,
The Celestial's bag of holding's location is uncertain.
Break the formation, what is there to fear ?
I used the Annihilation Restriction to deduce it
Dawn is coming soon.
and make this teleportation formation.
Face the wind, and don't dare to forget
inside the bag of holding.
that we're in this together.
No matter where you are on the outside,
Don't think of how we met, for our friendship is limitless.
as long as you use it,
no matter who steps inside,
it will lead here.
The journey we shared through the wind and the rain is now behind us.
But this formation is unstable,
Even if the flames of calamity burn, they cannot extinguish
it can only be used once.
our bond across time.
Be careful,
very careful.
Even the strongest winds cannot shatter
the loyalty and trust that shines within my heart.
Brother Xu,
A thousand li of faint mist after our parting,
one day, I will tell my mother
and life's ups and downs will continue.
that in my life of studying restrictions,
The leader always looks back when in a foreign land.
They hope their friends are well.
my greatest achievement
wasn't receiving the family's inheritance
but
using what I've learned
to help my best friend
defy the heavens to slay an Immortal !
Brother Xu,
one last thing.
Within this jade slip,
is the complete Annihilation Restriction of my Li Family.
On this journey, I'll forge a new path.
But without the Restriction Heart of the Ancestral Hall,
you can't use its full power.
I'll walk alone in this vast world before me.
It embodies generations of my family's efforts.
And you
The mountains and rivers gaze upon the wind,
are worthy of it !
together with me, we march forward.
A certain death
with no chance of survival...
Blood Ancestor's Cave
Thunder Celestial Realm
Will you talk or not ?
I...
only know that
his name is Xu Mu.
I really don't know...
Not knowing
is also a crime.
He's a member of the Yao Family.
My Lord,
these cultivators entered with our Temple's Thunder Cauldrons.
If they are all turned into slaves,
it may cause controversy.
If they've been disrespectful,
could we
hand them to the Temple to handle according to our laws ?
Laws ?
You guys
are merely soldiers patrolling on the Temple's behalf
and you think you can discuss laws with me ?
I respect the Thunder Celestial Temple
and won't break its laws.
But in this Allheaven Star System,
aside from your Thunder Celestial Temple,
the will of my Yao Family
also counts as laws.
The Yao Family and Thunder Celestial Temple
have always stayed out of each other's way.
This old man is handling business.
You people of the Thunder Celestial Temple
can scram !
In the name of Yao Kong,
I order all beings of the Thunder Celestial Realm !
All those marked with the slave seal
will dig into the ground
until they find Xu Mu.
Those who refuse
will die.
Those who hide from me
Those who know and don't report
will have their souls refined for 100 days !
Indiscriminate enslavement ?
He's crazy !
He treats us like insects...
This isn't a manhunt,
he's just venting his anger !
This is slaughter !
That guy called Xu Mu...
Who the hell is he !?
What the hell did he do to the Yao Family ?
That little guy of the Yao Family
has quite the temper.
This blood soul is very good,
it's actually been refined purer by an evil flame.
The bag's opening is sealed.
This Celestial's bag of holding has become a death trap.
It can be entered but not exited.
Blood Ancestor,
now...
it's time to lure you into the trap.
That was...
I found you.
Shattered Fragment
Thunder Celestial Realm
If this finger presses on,
Yao Xixue's soul will be annihilated !
I'll give you 3 sentences.
I thought that
Senior Blood Ancestor
would disregard Yao Xixue's life.
If I really kill this puppet of his,
he'll likely immediately harm Xixue.
The Blood Soul Pill
is not without its flaws.
Miss Yao is safe and sound,
Junior is willing to hand her over
so father and daughter can reunite.
I only have one condition:
you will swear on your Dao Heart
that you'll let me leave.
From then on, we'll be even,
and we'll never cross paths again.
Very well.
I swear on my Dao Heart
that if you hand over my daughter,
I
won't kill you.
Master,
can this old ghost's words be trusted ?
Master ?
Yao Xixue
is inside this formation.
Blood Ancestor,
the choice is yours.
If you enter the formation, I'll believe you.
If you chase me, it's a dead end.
It really is Xixue...
He took my daughter,
trapped her,
and still wants to negotiate ?
Dao Heart ?
I forgot to tell you.
This old man
doesn't believe in the heavens
nor in the Dao !
Refine !
Your puppet is decent.
It's a pity that
it was all in vain.
Break !
I already handed over Yao Xixue,
yet you insist on slaughtering me !?
Slaughtering you ?
No,
I won't kill you.
Your life,
from the moment you touched Xixue,
no longer belonged to you !
This is the puppet you refined.
It shall...
reunite with its master
together to the Underworld !
Blood Ancestor,
look at the formation in your hands.
Every moment it exists,
it grows more fragile.
You may be able to wait,
but can your daughter wait ?
This is the final warning.
If you still don't enter the formation,
Yao Xixue will be trapped forever !
He's actually using this to pressure me ?
Even my lie was within his calculations,
this brat
is pretty ruthless and quick-witted.
Explode !
Blood Ancestor,
can your daughter survive
the collapse of this space !?
Refining the puppet will take time.
Xixue's safety is my priority.
Alright,
I concede this round.
Xixue !
A Celestial's bag of holding ?
The exit is...
destroyed ?
Wang Lin,
You actually managed to get this far ?
I underestimated you !
But you
also underestimated a Nirvana Cleanser !
It's possible to forcibly freeze the teleportation formation ?
A Nirvana Cleanser
is truly terrifying !
However,
my plan
doesn't end there.
Explode !
Shatter !
Wang Lin,
was that all the tricks you know ?
I'm beyond annoyed !
Father !
Father, is that you ?
Xixue,
don't be afraid.
Father will take you out now !
So this was your plan all along ?
Collapsing the Celestial's bag of holding
to shatter everything inside ?
That way, the Blood Soul Pill will fail
and Xixue's soul will scatter.
Wang Lin,
when I get out of here,
I will tear you to pieces !
You
won't get out !
I failed to fulfill my promise to you,
I will make it up in the future.
Explode !
Father...
Are we...
Are we trapped here forever ?
Xixue,
don't be afraid.
The Blood Soul Pill...
Father !
Quickly take a Blood Soul Pill !
Next time, we will surely tear Wang Lin to pieces !
With my cultivation,
the Blood Soul Pill's revival is already useless.
No !
Father !
Don't !
I don't want to go alone !
Father, please don't !
Father...
The Blood God Token,
contains some of my blood.
This is bad !
With the token as the heart,
and the blood as the soul,
melt the soul into blood,
Become undying, indestructible !
Return to the origin,
reshape my body !
The time has come !
My husband is summoning me !
With the Soul Blood of 10 000 slaves,
help him melt his soul into blood.
Reunite
to form an indestructible body !
Little Ye !
My body is a sea of blood,
Blood Slaves are indestructible.
Blood Ancestor's split consciousness
Peak Late stage Ascendant
Blood Planet
My body
is undying !
Look,
it's beautiful !
Their lives are forging my husband's immortality !
The Blood Planet is extraordinary !
What glory is this !
Aren't you a slave too !?
Why must you help that evil tyrant ?
Silence !
I am the Blood Planet's Mistress.
You ants
aren't worthy of comparing yourselves to me !
All of you, shut up !
Is this the end ?
This world
is rotten to the core...
This is...
Using their bloodline as a catalyst,
he refined Blood Slaves
to make up for his own flaws
and reform his blood body.
This Nirvana Cleanser old monster
actually used such means
to become undying and indestructible.
The Celestial's bag of holding has collapsed.
In his current state,
he must be extremely weakened.
These needles, summoned by him,
are the only path to find him.
If I wait for him to recover,
no matter where I go,
I'll have nowhere to hide.
Although the Blood Ancestor's body was destroyed,
his soul remains.
It's still enough to easily kill me.
With my strength,
I'm afraid I can't beat the Blood Ancestor's soul.
A soul ?
Suitable souls are hard to find,
yet I happened to encounter such a fated beast.
I'll have to take this gamble.
Perfect !
Almost too perfect !
Only after being personally carved by me
can you really be called a true fated beast.
What is it !?
All of you, be quiet !
If you keep making noise, I'll twist off all your horns
and make them into a necklace for my fated beast !
Don't be afraid,
they're jealous of you.
Only you are special.
What did you sense ?
A blood soul ?
Fated !
Truly fated !
10 000 bloods return to the origin !
Blood Ancestor's Blood Body
Thunder Celestial Realm
You happened to find that place...
Shameless Junior,
you're the one who walked into a trap !
Do you know what the words "Nirvana Cleanser" mean !?
Even if my Origin Soul was damaged,
I can kill you
with a single thought !
I know I'm no match for Senior.
But this time,
there is no turning back !
Senior,
show yourself !
It's fate !
What a good blood soul !
He really came !
This person is eccentric,
I wonder if he'll do as I predicted.
Help ?
You're foolish !
In Allheaven,
who will dare to offend the Yao Family for you ?
Senior,
Junior's name is Yao Kong,
I'm the grandson of the Blood God.
Please Senior, help me condense my blood body.
The Yao Family will reward you greatly !
The Blood God's grandson ?
The Yao Family ?
Fine,
I'll do you a favor
and lend you a hand.
Thank you, Senior !
Wang Lin !
Wait a moment.
Yao Family kid,
you and I are fated !
Just now, you asked me for help.
We are now bound by fate.
However,
now...
it's time for you to return the favor !
Half the blood body ?
He even exceeded my expectations.
How
dare you !?
You asked me,
and I agreed.
This half of your blood body is your repayment.
Now,
we're even !
Damn you, Wang Lin !
You summoned this person,
not to join forces with him,
but to lure me into speaking first
and letting him rightfully steal my essence !
Senior, wait !
Little guy,
don't think I don't know what you're scheming.
Don't push your luck.
Do you really think I won't cut you down ?
Junior wouldn't dare.
It's just that, regarding what just happened,
even if Junior knows Senior dislikes being indebted,
if you think about it,
Senior now owes Junior a favor, at least some wisdom.
Bullshit !
I... I...
How troublesome !
Truly troublesome !
I'll give you some credit for being ruthless.
I never owe favors !
For the sake of the fated beast,
I'll give you this thunder orb I refined.
Use it for the killing blow.
It's enough to save your life.
The favor is now repaid.
If you scheme against me again,
I'll cut you down !
Wang Lin !
That was a clever scheme, using a borrowed blade to weaken me...
I truly underestimated your schemes !
From the moment I stepped into this fight,
I never expected to retreat unscathed.
I have no way out !
Mountain Soul !
Heavenly
Chop !
Stop !
This strike
should be enough !
Your schemes
and your spells
have impressed me.
But,
it ends here !
Split consciousness,
Soul Devour !
I'll pour my blood into your body
to devour your Origin Soul !
Whether it's my Nirvana Cleanser spells
or my Yao Family's inheritance,
they're beyond your comprehension !
In the end...
I was still defeated...
Spatial Rift
Thunder Celestial Realm
Fiend,
wake up !
Wake up quickly !
Oh no, oh no !
Master !
Master !!!
Wang Lin's
Sea of Consciousness
The might of a Nirvana Cleanser...
The power of the Yao Family...
What a powerhouse with limitless power !
And now, I...
have exhausted all my strength.
Defeated by fate,
defeated by circumstances,
defeated by...
this world of unequal birth.
He was born with everything.
But I had to cultivate from scratch
for a thousand years.
I was repeatedly toyed with by fate.
So, in these 1000 years,
who have I ever relied on ?
At every step,
I had to fight with my own strength.
This world is heartless.
Empty Planet
Alliance Star System
The avatar is about to die.
The bloodline resonance
awakened me.
Wang Lin's original body
Pseudo 4-stars Ancient God
Blood Ancestor,
you deserve to die.
We're separated by star systems.
The Alliance and Allheaven
are too far away.
My body cannot reach it.
I might be trapped here.
But Blood Ancestor,
since you made a move on my avatar,
I will cross the sea of stars,
and I will destroy your Blood Planet !
Hurry up !
Keep moving.
Little Ye !
I lended a hand to the Blood Ancestor,
Blood Ancestor's split consciousness
Peak Late stage Ascendant
Blood Planet
it counts as a high merit !
When the Blood Ancestor returns,
my position as a concubine
will be unshakable !
Who dares
to offend the Blood Planet !?
It's you !?
Senior Brother...
Is it dawn ?
Shatter !
And who are you exactly ?
For an ant's body,
a single thread of my consciousness
is enough to crush you a thousand times !
The Blood Planet is collapsing !
Break the chains !
Fight your way out !
I won't let you trample
on the legacy I built for over 10 000 years !
Noisy !
This aura...
You're an Ancient G...
Impossible...
This is impossible !
Blood Ancestor...
My Lord Blood Ancestor,
save me !
Thank you, Senior !
Leave quickly.
Explode !
Senior Brother,
we're saved !
My origin was destroyed...
The Blood Planet was destroyed,
your power is severed.
With all my strength, I will slay that Immortal.
Avatar,
it's time to wake up.
The Blood Ancestor lost his foundation.
This blood body is now at its limit.
Good !
You want to refine me with this body ?
Then I'll play along with you
and use your 10 000-year-old cultivation
to lay my foundation for Illusory Yin !
Blood Ancestor's Blood Body
Thunder Celestial Realm
Corporeal Yang
(former Nirvana Cleanser)
A tribulation of this magnitude ?
But he's just reaching the second step !
My blood body
is being refined !?
Fiend,
wake up !
Wang Lin's avatar
Illusory Yin
Well...
Very well !
How dare you...
How dare you refine my blood body
as the foundation for your breakthrough !?
Even if my cultivation fell to Corporeal Yang,
it's more than enough to kill
a new Illusory Yin !
Come,
you and I,
have yet to fight for real !
Then I...
will oblige !
This strike
is to pay for the crime of imprisoning my daughter !
Master,
the realm gap is still too great !
A wise man doesn't fight when the odds are against him.
Let's flee !
It's not over yet.
How can we know who will live or die !?
Blood River Stamp !
This strike
is to pay for destroying my blood body !
Blood Explosion !
This strike
is to pay for the fate of the Blood Planet !
With a rogue cultivator's fate,
you dare to say you'll slay an Immortal !?
Absurd !
Your last trump card
is just that thunder orb given by that old ghost
of the Thunder Celestial Temple.
Just watch
whether it can shake me at all !
That gift,
whether it's wisdom
or a scam...
I got so far through my own hard work !
Senior's cultivation is sky-high.
I'm no match for you.
But...
What if I were also at the Corporeal Yang realm !?
I was born in the wilderness,
and walked through thorns.
A thousand years of cultivating
with every step soaked in blood...
I've long since been used to not relying on the heavens and the earth,
nor on others.
One man
can be a soldier,
a general,
but he can also be...
a whole army !
If I have no mountain to lean on,
I will become the mountain !
This is...
the Heaven's Might !
Divine Retribution !?
I...
I've never seen a tribulation of this magnitude !
He just broke through to Illusory Yin
and forcibly raised his cultivation to Corporeal Yang ?
The heavens won't tolerate that.
The heavens
are out to kill him !
Evacuate quickly !
This Divine Retribution
isn't something a Celestial Lord can survive !
Hurry up, go !
You're trying to use Heaven's Might to drag me down with you ?
You're a madman !
Didn't Senior want my life ?
Get lost !
You're courting death by yourself,
don't drag me down with you !
It's too late !
Blood Seal !
Wang Lin,
I abandon this blood body.
Just wait here and die !
Who told you
that I feared thunder ?
My Origin Soul
is an Ancient Thunder Dragon !
I won't ask the heavens, I'll ask my heart
if I'm willing to defy and to slay an Immortal.
I'll draw my sword, and won't come back until the victory is mine.
You've got a good grasp of things.
Trapped in a dead end, I can only fight for my life.
I am determined
That's worthy of being fated with me.
to face my opponent head-on.
The more a blade is sharpened,
the more dazzling it becomes.
Please cut through the mountains and rivers that trap my heart.
If I wash my sword in the wind and the snow,
then even a calamity will lead me to the summit of the clouds.
Whether it's a God, a Demon, a monster or an Immortal,
those who wrong me don't need to expect forgiveness.
Why bother relying on the wind
when wildfires are destined to set these plains ablaze ?
My lone self faces the setting sun,
alone but fearless.
I stay true to my heart with no regrets.
As I walk against the current,
I rise to the challenge with my unwavering resolve.
Wang Lin's avatar
Corporeal Yang
No pity, no complaint, I just walk forward.
No mountain to lean on, I'll rely on myself to overcome a thousand trials.
The origin energy within me
is somewhat out of control.
I don't believe in the heavens, I don't fear power, I'll tame the darkness
It's as if it no longer belongs to me,
a thousand times, like a blazing flame.
but belongs to the world.
If my origin energy can merge with the world,
Celestial Fragment Stamp
Tribulation artifact
I won't ask the heavens, I'll ask my heart
if I'm willing to defy and to slay an Immortal.
then my Origin Soul and my body
I'll draw my sword, and won't come back until the victory is mine.
should be able to do the same.
Trapped in a dead end, I can only fight for my life.
I am determined
to face my opponent head on.
This feeling is not a hindrance,
The more a blade is sharpened,
the more dazzling it becomes.
but rather a kind of hidden enlightenment.
Please cut through the mountains and rivers that trap my heart.
Could this be...
If I wash my sword in the wind and the snow,
the true meaning of the Illusory Yin and Corporeal Yang realms ?
then even a calamity will lead me to the summit of the clouds.
Time to settle this.
I must quickly find a body to possess
and restore my Nirvana Cleanser cultivation !
This brat
has become a serious threat !
Blood Ancestor !
Just like you chased me before,
it's now...
my turn to chase.
No pity, no complaint, I just walk forward.
No mountain to lean on, I'll rely on myself to overcome a thousand trials.
I don't believe in the heavens, I don't fear power, I'll tame the darkness
Spatial Bending !?
This brat just entered the second step,
a thousand times, like a blazing flame.
how does he know this Nirvana Scryer spell ?
I won't ask the heavens, I'll ask my heart
if I'm willing to defy and to slay an Immortal.
I'll draw my sword, and won't come back until the victory is mine.
This move
is for you relying on your cultivation
to bully me and force me into a corner
Trapped in a dead end, I can only fight for my life.
I am determined
when I was weak and helpless.
to face my opponent head-on.
I judge you
arrogant !
The more a blade is sharpened,
the more dazzling it becomes.
Please cut through the mountains and rivers that trap my heart.
If I wash my sword in the wind and the snow,
then even a calamity will lead me to the summit of the clouds.
All beings bow their heads, only I hold mine up high.
This move
Who do I roar for ? For this vast sky.
is for you relying on your noble bloodline
and looking down on others.
I judge you
I don't bow to the heavens, but to my own courage,
to my fiery spirit.
lowly !
Although the mortal world brings countless calamities and hardships,
they forge my Daoist spirit to be as steadfast as a mountain.
If the world is a crimson-blood wasteland,
why did you waste words in this battle ?
This whip
is for your arrogance,
This heart has remained unchanged for a thousand years.
for ignoring right and wrong,
and deciding my life and death !
If an Immortal is in my way, then I shall slay that Immortal !
I judge you
worthy of execution !
I came from the depths,
I'm used to cold arrows and hidden blades.
I know fate won't grant me salvation.
They treat this mortal world as worthless as grass,
thunder dares to burn the wilderness,
but doesn't dare to bend my spine.
Who isn't born with pride ?
Don't dare to bow to hardships.
I'm a Nirvana Cleanser powerhouse,
the Ancestor of the Blood Planet !
You want to use your soul to control me ?
Wishful thinking !
Blood
God,
explode !
Blood Ancestor,
if you self-destruct,
both your body and soul will die,
never to be reborn.
If you want to see your daughter again,
then offer your soul to the flag.
There may still be a sliver of a chance.
Xixue...
So be it.
All-Seer...
Ling Tianhou...
Blood Ancestor...
This is what Immortals are like.
So what
if they're Immortals ?
If the heavens get in my way,
I will defy the heavens !
If an Immortal wants to kill me,
I'll become the Immortal Slayer !
If I have no
mountain to lean on,
I will become
the mountain !
If I have no
one to rely on,
I will become
the heavens !
Wang Lin's original body isn't a fully fledged 4-stars Ancient God, he is stuck with an illusory fourth star that's incomplete. Its power level is around Illusory Yin / Corporeal Yang.
The fragment of the Thunder Celestial Realm Wang Lin was on when he faced his tribulation was refined into a stamp artifact.
The whole structure of the Thunder Celestial Realm's story arc was rewritten to fit all these events in a single movie.
Even a mortal can slay an Immortal.
Even if a thousand dangers lie ahead,
no matter how high the mountain, I'll climb it.
My fate is mine alone,
I'm not afraid.
If the ocean trench is like a rift in the sky,
I'll become a mountain to tread the cloudy summit.
Rain like crimson ink, sword like a brush, I continue to write
the reincarnation cycle.
The wild grass buried the shore of the past.
The cold night never had lamplight for company.
Fate is carved into bone-chilling cold.
I only accept suffering,
not willing to lament.
Being born with nothing isn't tragic.
Tragedy is willingly bowing and accepting decay.
How many shackles are inscribed with fate's lament ?
I refuse to believe blood defines your rank.
Isn't the so-called fate meant to be rewritten ?
In a desperate situation, there is no path of retreat.
I will break the chains of reincarnation by my own hands.
No need to profile me, no compromise, no kneeling to the heavens.
Wind and rain rage on,
I hear the thunder rumbling.
Every scar
turns into a burden I bear.
No need for anyone to bestow me
with a talented body.
Emerging from the depths,
I possess my own vastness.
Even a mortal can slay an Immortal.
Even if a thousand dangers lie ahead,
no matter how high the mountain, I'll climb it.
My fate is mine alone,
I'm not afraid.
If the ocean trench is like a rift in the sky,
I'll become a mountain to tread the cloudy summit.
Rain like crimson ink, sword like a brush, I continue to write
the reincarnation cycle.
Fate's shackles imprison people, with no one to confide in to see through life and death.
Reincarnation was reshaped by me !
A thousand trials can't bind my pride, old chapters were turned.
One sword breaks the thick fog,
Righteous path or demonic, mortals are only fit to bow.
The chains that bind me don't mean I've surrendered.
Once the mind's steadied, the shackles are dismantled.
In the wilderness, walking alone.
Hardships !
Some loneliness is destined.
A thousand years !
When I scatter and
spread !
My fate is destined to be the summit.
Let me break all prejudices,
shatter the suspense of the unknown,
embrace the tempering of fire and frost.
Those who once looked down will look up at my transformation.
If I have no mountain to lean on,
I will become the mountain.
If I have no one to depend on,
I will become the heavens.
I shall ultimately stand as a lone wolf.
Wang Lin !